schoolhouseelectric.com 2019-01-21

# Privacy Policy | Schoolhouse

### GENERAL STATEMENT

Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. respects the privacy of all individuals visiting our website. This Privacy Policy will outline what type of information Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. will collect and what may be done with this information. Schoolhouse Electric Supply Co. reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. In that case, the changes will be posted here.

### PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Personally-identifiable information (such as your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number) will not be collected unless given by you voluntarily and knowingly. In the case that you do submit personally-identifiable information to us, it may be stored and used by Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. to contact you. Your personally-identifiable information WILL NOT be sold or given to a third party for use in marketing or solicitation. Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. will confidentially maintain your personal information and will use it only to enhance or support your relationship with Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. It is possible, however, that Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. may be forced to disclose your information to the government or another third party in certain circumstances.

While Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. will work hard to keep your personal information private, it is possible that a third party could intercept your information illegally. If, to our knowledge, this occurs, Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. will contact you in order to explain the situation.

Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. does not intend to collect or maintain personally-identifiable information from children under the age of eighteen. If a child does submit this type of information to Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co., a parent or guardian should contact us using the contact information provided at the bottom of this page.

If you would like to remove your information from our database, change your information, or opt out of receiving communication from Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co., you may contact us using the contact information provided at the bottom of this page.

### OTHER INFORMATION AND “COOKIES”

Certain information that is not personally-identifiable (such as your internet browser, operating system, and IP address) may be collected automatically. When you visit our site, your computer may receive a “cookie” from Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co.. This “cookie” will be stored on your computer and used to collect information. Most internet browsers will allow you to block or erase “cookies” from your hard drive. Please refer to your browser’s help section to learn more about this.

### SECURITY

While Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co. will work to maintain your security, no internet data transmission is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of your information.

### THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

This Privacy Policy applies only to Schoolhouse Electric & Supply Co., and not to any other company or website.

### CONTROLLING YOU PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have previously agreed to Schoolhouse using your personal information for marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time and opt out through your options in your [My Account](https://www.schoolhouse.com/account/login) section when logged in, unsubscribe link within our marketing emails or contacting us at [customersupport@schoolhouse.com](mailto:customersupport@schoolhouse.com). You can also opt-out of cookie use below.
